hidden-street.net 2006-05-30

# Hidden Street

**Privacy Policy**

Hidden Street respects and is committed to protect the privacy of visitors to this website. This privacy policy tells you what information we collect from you, and how we may use it.

**Information collected by Hidden Street**

Visiting this website will enable us to automatically collect information such as the type of browser you're using and your IP address, via the use of statistical orogram deployments. We use these information to re-evaluate our site's layout and design to enable us to provide a more user-friendly website, as well as provide the right content for the right type of audience.

User-supplied information collected through the registration process, entry forms, polls or other similar vehicles is used to improve the content of our website, or used for any marketing endeavours that we may pursue in the future. Information collected is not shared with other organisations for commercial purposes unless specifically stated.

**Public forums**

This site makes use of forums available to its users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We respect freedom of speech and request that users respect one another in exercising said freedom. However, any messages that we find distasteful will be deleted by our moderators and administrator of the forum.

**General**

This site contains links to other sites. Hidden Street is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Contacting Hidden Street**

Should you have any questions about this privacy policy, you may contact us at: hiddenstreetgmail.com

Copyright © 2004-2006 Hidden Street. [Privacy Policy](http://www.hidden-street.net/privacy.php)  
Best viewed with Mozilla Firefox
